question_data = [
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "'Typewriter' is the longest word that can be typed using only the first row on a QWERTY "
                    "keyboard.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "There are 86400 seconds in a day.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "An eggplant is a vegetable.",
        "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The bikini is named after the 'Bikini Atoll', an island where the United States "
                    "conducted tests on atomic bombs.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Sitting for more than three hours a day can cut two years off a person's life expectancy.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The French word to travel is 'Travail'",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Fast food restaurant chains Carl's Jr. and Hardee's are owned by the same company.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "'Santa Claus' is a variety of melon.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The scientific name for the Southern Lights is Aurora Australis?",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the "
                    "streets of Chicago.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    }
]
